Something that is actually my strong side, you know what it is
It's not to shut up and let me talk in a Mukbang once.
Right.
Just
No now you should look boring it is when I shut up.
What am I a sack of potatoes or?
I love potatoes though.
Klara talked so much in the last Mukbangen and many asked why I was so quiet.
You have to learn to let other people talk so
*Interrupts each other*
I'll keep quiet huh. - Yes.
Yeah..what is not school end
I haven't put parking on my car.
Haven't you done that
No .. Armin
What have you had .. should we hug or should we bowl
Wait, wait, hug .. I felt a bit like a thunderstorm when I came in here.
Why does this apple juice taste
What have you done
Now she starts again.
Yes anyway.
It's just you and you.
This I think we should taste.
Choco Blanco.
You were damn in fourth place
*ruffles*
Can you stop cutting it on .. wait a stop.
Now I have no plate.
This would be the slash plate.
You have taken the slash plate on my ...
Now you have spilled on my trousers too.
I am actually celebrating years.
Yeah
In two days.
How does it feel like you turn 29
Can we talk about that my plate is now wet - Häääär, Häääär, Hääär !!!
But stop I'm not done
Then it becomes it ..
How are you darling
Thanks for the question, it only took 15 minutes into the intro until you asked.
Them will get a wrong picture of me, am not i nice
Same with 25.
Do you still know the adult or do you just know no
Do you understand what I mean
So I would say this: I understand exactly what you mean.
When I was 22, I felt that I was type 15.
But now I'm an adult.
I can manage myself, I know how to cook pasta etc.
I mean life.
Well
No I still like to tramples just as much.
So, for example, when I have children ...
I will tramp very much.
I will be the one who just "should you have melon cheated!"
I will be that person.
Still, I never think I will grow up.
When people ask me how old I am:
And I will have to say thirty so I'll just ... Do you start feeling sensible?
No.
You don't understand anything from what I'm saying.
If you like me mail, I like.
No love here.
I will actually write down my bank account here in the description.
"Swisha an optional sum."
Label it with Klara's birthday.
It would have been fun if you swish any sum, my number is on Instagram.
Congratulations then.
Thanks.
Now summer is here.
- Yes, speaking of summer, do you know what I heard on the internet this morning?
"I read on the internet that ..."
No now I have grown old for real.
I've heard about it.
What the hell is that about
I say no
Why do you care you have summer vacation whenever you want.
True ..
You go to Ibiza a little here and there.
It's true.
They said that the summer holidays should not be 10 weeks but it should be type 6.
You are not affected by it.
I felt like this .. If there is something we need more then it is f*cing leave.
More money ..
*mumbles*
As we talked about in the last section.
I just thought it is probably not good to shorten it too much.
I think people feel good about having 8 weeks of vacation and taking it easy.
Do you feel the pollen
For the first time in my life I do.
I've never known it.
For the thing is like this.
I was sick a few months ago and went on the shit that everyone else had.
And I was stuffed in connection with that.
I was stuffed in connection with that.
It was several months ago.
After all, I was cold and thought "my nasal congestion goes over soon."
When I'm healthy.
It still lasts.
It has lasted several months and I take nasal spray every day.
And I have begun to realize then that it is clear as hell that it is pollen.
It's pollen 100%.
I have never felt that ever
I tried to go pretty cheap anyway.
I have 5 more ..
The thing is that I should buy another one.
The thing is that I bought the whole house.
I bought the entire property.
So we will build a big fucking house.
We will have three balconies and five outdoor pools.
Out towards the horizon, they should go.
Do you have a room for me
No
Shit what I shudder when I talk like that.
Not late.
Have I snatched no I haven't cheated anything.
Not late but it's 100% easy.
Last, when was it
It may surely be that I have palled an apple or something.
Pall an apple from a tree, they are free.
Are you the way that goes in the store, opens a banana and eat on it
No, but when I'm with the kids and they say * I'm really sucking * I say type "Eat."
Then I always pay.
I save the banana peel so they can scan it.
So you can't do iofs.
Everything sits and looks at me where it should sit.
Compare me then, my stuff sits like this.
Mine is looking up.
Yours sits *ding *
Gooood morning
Do you know what my tits are actually good.
Is it something I really like ..
In addition to money
And my tits.
Well
That too.
It's risifrutti.
It's something I ... but it's actually a little fun.
When you go on an excursion with school
That's exactly what I would say.
No you shouldn't say what I would say.
Nehe.
Now you are talking to me.
Yes for once.
Can you stop looking at me
Croat or Serb.
Maybe pole, i don't know
Yes, but because you do not look Swedish for five cents.
Liberal no wait what is it, Libanes?
Svenne
No.
No
What will you do this summer
So Croatia opens its boundaries now on the 15th.
No
But the thing is that I think nothing is open down there.
So it will be closed, half closed.
It's fine for me I live in Jannie and Jon's castle.
Yeah you like sliding on your friends' shrimp sandwich
That's what I usually do.
Like you usually pay my bills and such.
Yes you grew up on Youtube because of me.
Yes we have talked about that.
*Antonija rap*
But do we have to be like a bowl?
I actually became it thanks to you.
To appreciate each other.
You know I did a lashlift now.
Do you appreciate me
Yes I talked about it then because I said then that I want it as ready.
And then I went in and scroll and just: "What is this"
She just: "But it's medium bend"
And I just: "What is ready for something"
She just: "Medium" so I said I want as clear.
You are a little in love with me.
Yes it's me.
But you don't admit it.
Or if Antonija posted like this "inspo bathroom" the other day.
Yes it is my bathroom you have described.
But it was actually she who decided.
Yes but you have probably said what you want.
You just: "So I think a little you know gray walls, black taps"
It was exactly the same disc cone with bud.
I think it's great fun.
But you can never give it to me ever.
Why can't you give me, I like you.
There they came there too.
Equally stressed every time.
It's like when the invoice for the rent will be asked no!
Not again!
So I'm so damn tired of paying invoices.
It's something I don't want to do when I'm getting big.
Pay invoices.
So it's really like this: "Damn what a lot of money I make now, come in as much cash as possible and then just"
It goes like this.
No it goes like this and then just down and then just up.
Yes but how fun is that
How long should I have to work because I have no fucking Medelström who goes on this situation.
SEK 55,000.
You don't do that at all.
Well, I do.
Then you have done it now.
No I have been doing it for a few months now.
But shut up because I know we take the same salary.
Yes but after that I have taken out more so that I will fucking get an apartment.
Oops.
You know that .. Yes okay ...
I call the auditor and only: "We have to raise the salary"
Oh
He was in the sun for a long time.
Now we have to stop talking money.
Because then these are the ones happening.
Burnt brains.
I'll say a thing.
I have gone into the wall.
Hello after this, I just want to say it when this one has come up.
Then my other has come up because after this we will eat dessert.
Cake
Because it's my birthday.
I like to be kissed like this.
Did you know that these numbers are minutes.
Well, no I didn't know.
That is sick.
I thought it was level 2.
This is totally sick.
But who wants it for 7 minutes then it becomes like a damn brick.
Do not understand.
What do they even mean
No clue.
Do you think I'm finer without fringes
Much finer, it was a bit trashy before.
Yes.
But I think you are very nice.
But what I don't understand is why you don't have mascara on the lashes
Because I kind of think it weighs down my eyes.
No.
I promise.
So we are so damn awesome, thank you for following us, thank you for sitting and jawing with us.
See you next week maybe.
We'll do that.
It sounds good to say so, see you next week, kiss pussy, bye
It sounds like we have a TV show, so we should have that.
So TV contact me, or us.
TV, Internet.
Internet.
Internet Contact us We want a talk show.